I have built hundreds of AI agents and
in this video I'll show you the six
agents that everyone needs and I'll also
explain how to turn this into a
profitable side hustle and no it's not
by building an automation agency. So to
build AI agents NA10 is the simplest way
by far. It is more powerful than
make.com's API and it is easy to get
started and you can basically build any
AI agent you want inside of NA10. So
let's start with the trigger and again
there are hundreds of different options.
For example, if you select on app event,
you can select from thousands of
different apps that are natively
connected into any. However, for this
build, I'm actually going to go with the
schedule trigger. This is one of the
most useful types of triggers inside of
any, which lets you set an interval.
Could be days, could be hours, even
seconds, right? I'm going to go with
days once a day. So, the first agent I'm
going to be building is an infinite lead
followup. And this is what it's going to
look like when it's finished. But
basically, it will follow up with any
types of leads. could be job candidates,
could be potential clients, and it's
going to keep following up until you get
the sale. So once you decide on the
schedule, next you need the first action
step, right? What is the first thing the
AI agent should do after we call him? In
this case, it needs to be Gmail get many
messages. There it is. So it can analyze
multiple different emails that you
received and decide what actions it
wants to take on those emails. Now, this
is very important. Anytime you make any
change inside of any 10, make sure to
click save. Otherwise, you risk losing
progress. So, inside of the Gmail node,
we need to select which email do we want
our AI agent to look at. Right? So, if
you don't have any emails connected,
simply click on create new credential.
And this is actually probably the
hardest part. So, if you're willing to
sit through the next 3 minutes, you will
already be ahead of 99% of people. And I
can promise you that because most people
cannot even set up a single Google
service into their AI agent and they're
just going to drop off and never
automate anything in their life. So if
you can stick through the next three
minutes, you will begin your automation
journey and you can get rid of all the
boring in your life. So what we
need to do is we need to go to Google
Cloud Console. So let me show you how to
do that. This is going to be the email
inbox I'm going to be automating and
anything I send out, it's going to
automatically get follow-ups. So if you
send out a job application, it's going
to keep following up with that company
until they respond to you. Same with,
you know, getting clients as a business,
whatever you want to do. This agent is
universal. Everyone needs him. So to set
this up, we need to go into Google and
type in Google Cloud Console. Boom. Hit
enter. Click the first link. Now make
sure to switch to the same account you
want to automate. Now at the top, we
need to create a project, right? Create
project. New project. Let's name it NA10
email follow upper. I know very creative
name. For location, just leave it as is.
Click create. And this is how Google
Cloud Console works. Basically, you have
these different projects and in these
you have these off clients. You don't
have to understand all of it. Just
follow what I'm doing. Follow these
steps. I'm going to show you everything
in this video. So, you can see the
project has been created. Click on
select project. And you need to see it
in the top. There we go. NA10 email
follow-uper. Beautiful. Since we're
going to be using Gmail, we need to type
in Gmail API and we need to enable this.
There we go. Enable. Literally just one
click. Takes a few seconds to load and
it's going to enable it for this
project. And boom. Just like that, it's
enabled. So, let's click on OAF consent
screen and then click on clients. We
need to create a new client. Get
started. So app name I'm going to name
David Andre and A10 agent. Support email
just select the email you're automating.
Next audience you can only select
external. If you have a Google Workspace
you can select internal but just click
on external. Next email address just
paste the same one. Next. And then agree
continue. Create. All right. So all of
configuration created. So let's click on
clients on the left again. Create
client. And this is the last step. So
web application. We can rename this as
NA10 followup agent. And here is the
important part, right? So if we go back
into NA10, we can see that this is the
redirect URL. So copy that. Boom.
Authorized redirect URLs. Paste this in.
Create. The next two things is the
client ID and the client secret. So we
get those when you click create. So
client ID, just copy paste those. Boom.
Client secret. Just like that. Copy
paste. And then click on save. And next
we need to click on this button which
appears after you fill this out. Sign
with Google. And this is really the last
stretch. So we need to select the email.
We have a access block. Let's see. App
is being tested. Okay. So we I think I
didn't add myself as a developer. That's
a mistake. Let's go back to our client
audience. Test users. There we go. Need
to add myself as a test user. Save.
Nice. So now we can continue, but it
doesn't seem like it. You might see,
okay, David, this is another error.
Actually, it's not. It's just bad UI. We
need to click on continue. Right. It's
it's kind of tempting to click on back
to safety, but don't worry. We're
absolutely safe here. Just click on
continue and then u it's the permissions
you want the AI agent to have. So I want
my full email management. Continue and
connection successful. Now we did the
hardest part low key. Now just building
the agent is going to be much easier and
this is going to compound to all the
other agents. So keep in mind this is
only the first of six AI agents that I'm
going to show you. And each of them you
can take the lessons from this one and
just build them that much faster. And
honestly if you implement all six of
these agents into your life, you're
going to save multiple hours per week.
Now, before we add the AI agent, there
are actually a few other things we have
to do inside of the Gmail note. First of
all, make sure to enable return all.
Leave simplify turned on. And then
inside of filters, this is super
important. We need to click on search
and do in send. This is the same search
you can do inside of Gmail. Just do in
send. Now, it's funny because I've never
sent an email from this Gmail address,
but for most emails, you probably use
them to send stuff as well. You can also
do something like has attachment,
whatever works inside of Gmail. This is
the same logic that will work in this
NA10 node. So this since it's a
following up agent, we need to check
which emails we send so that it can
follow up on them with that recipient.
So this is it like this note is good. So
we can save that and actually we can run
it so we can test out if it works. So
get many messages. Let's see. And as
expected we have no output data because
we didn't send an emails. But let me
just quickly send an email to myself.
Boom. Hi David, how are you doing?
testing anything at the moment. Let me
know how it goes. All right. So, I'm
just going to send one email so we have
some data to work with. And now we have
actually something in the send. So,
let's go back and let's rerun this so we
can see if our node works. And there we
go. One item. So, just like that, we
have proven that our first two nodes
work. The schedule trigger will be
executed once a day. And then the Gmail
will successfully pull all sent emails
from your inbox that you just connected
and you get all the data whether it's
the history ID, the internal date, the
payload, the subject line or the
recipient. Everything you might need is
in this output data which of course
we're going to use to feed that into an
agent to process it to write a
personalized short follow-up message.
Okay, so let's click on save. Now the
next note I'm actually going to use a
code note. This one is the most
customizable note. You can either use
JavaScript or Python. I'm going to use
JavaScript. So, I'm going to replace
this default. I'm going to delete all of
it with something I prepared ahead of
time just to save you guys time. Now,
you might be thinking, "Okay, David, how
can I create this? This is so complex."
Calm down. I'm going to show you. You
can literally do this with JGBT. So,
inside of JBT, you need to describe what
you want. Here's how that looks like for
this agent. Build a function that
processes Gmail messages data to find
friends where you reached out but never
got a response. So all of this, you
know, you don't have to understand
JavaScript as long as you can describe
what exactly you want. You can build
essentially anything. Just make sure to
use CH GB thinking because it's a lot
more powerful than the default GPD5. So
once CHGBD finishes generating the code,
just click copy code right here at the
top of the code block. Go back into NA10
and paste it inside of your JavaScript
node. So just like with every single new
node we add, we should test it. You
should never build a full automation
without doing any testing because then
you're going to be stuck in many
different errors, right? You want to fix
the errors one by one as you're building
it. So, let's run this node. Boom. Node
executed successfully. And let's look at
the output here. Now, the simplest way
to explain this is that this code, it
basically finds all the emails where you
didn't get a response, right? This is
like all the failed outreaches because
you don't want the agent to be running
on the ones that did get a response. So,
this one finds the ones that failed and
gets their thread IDs. That's just how
Gmail notifies them. Basically, those
are the people who completely ignored
you because those are the ones we need
to follow up with. Okay, so the next
note after this one is going to be a
loop loop over items. Boom. There we go.
And here we don't have to literally do
any setup. It's as simple as possible
because it's going to run on our AI
agent. So, we need to replace this node.
We need to delete it and replace it with
something else. So, let's click on plus.
And inside is going to be our AI agent.
This is going to be the decision maker
of how do we follow up, right? What the
message looks like, how does the email
look like. So let's click on save and
let's configure the AI agent. Now to do
that let's quickly run the loop node.
Super simple and then we have some input
data in the AI agent to work with.
Right? So let's customize the pro
message. We need to click on define
below and then click on expression. Now
if you just look at the left side of the
data which is always the input, right? A
lot of people are confused by NA10
because if you're using for the first
time, it might seem intimidating. But
when you realize that the left side,
this side is just the input data. The
middle is the current node, aka what we
do with that data. And the right side is
the output. So what the data looks like
after this node is executed. Once you
understand this, the UI doesn't look so
intimidating. So if you look on the
left, what do we need, right? Well, we
need the subject and we probably need
the snippet. So we just need to define
something like this where we say subject
and then JSON.ubject which by the way
let me show you a pro trick. You can
just drag it over. This is the beauty of
NA10. So when you identify the data you
want just literally drag it over and
just like that boom it's there. So
whether you're like oh David you
pre-prepared this. I don't know how to
do it. All you need to do is really drag
stuff from the left into the middle to
kind of build your prompt. That's the
essential skill when using the AI agent
inside of NA10. Now the snippet again,
same thing, right? This text is just so
we tell the agent this is the snippet.
Boom. You can literally rename this like
here's the email body, whatever you want
it to be, you know, just type it in
there. This is the user prompt. This is
telling the agent what the email is
about. However, the user prompt is not
enough. We also need a system prompt.
So, let's click on add options system
message. And this is where we're going
to tell the AI agent how to behave. So
once again, let's switch to expression
because you can click this button to
make it full screen, which is much
easier to edit. And again, I prepared
this ahead of time, but feel free to
pause and copy it. By the way, all of
the AI agents, all of the prompts,
everything from this video is inside of
the classroom of the new society. So
when you go to templates and presets
right here, you can literally get all
the AI agents from my past videos as
well as from this video and just copy
paste them into your life and business.
So actually inside of any 10 what you
can do is click on these three dots in
the top and click on import from file
and then you can select a JSON file
which is a pre-built agent and boom just
like that I imported the full AI agent
already configured into my NA10. So if
you want to just skip through a lot of
steps maybe you're a busy business owner
you don't have time join the new society
go into the classroom click on templates
and presets and here you can access all
of my agents all my pre-built
automations all of my prompts and
instructions everything you need to
start automating your life and business.
The link to new society is going to be
below the video. Now, back to NA10. So,
I'm going to delete this because I'm
showing you how to build it from
scratch, but that was just for you that
want to skip through some steps. Let's
define the AI agent. So, we have the
system prompt again. Uh it just defines
the behavior of it, right? So, what the
task is, input explanation, how the
output should look like, the tone and
style, basic pro engineering. You can
customize this for how you want your
emails to look. Obviously, we still get
an error inside of the AI agent. And the
reason is we're lacking the chat model.
Without the LLM, without the large
language model, the AI agent is just a
body without a brain. The LLM is the
brain. It's what gives it the
intelligence. Now, you can either use
OpenAI for models like GPT. You can use
Enthropic for the cloud models, Google
for Gemini models, or you can use Open
Router to access all of the models. Now,
most of you are probably familiar with
CHI GBD. So, we're going to stick to
OpenAI. and it's also one of the
simplest to set up. For the model, I
would like to use GPD 4.1. This is one
of the most reliable models in the world
right now. It's much more reliable than
GPD5, and sometimes it's even better to
be honest, especially in agentic
workflows. So, let's select that. Now,
our automation is a bit messy. I don't
like when it looks ugly, but we're going
to fix that in a bit. The main part is
we need to define the credential, right?
So, this is basically the OpenAI API
key. As you can see, I already have a
few, but if you don't have any, just go
to Google again and type in platform
OpenAI.
Boom. And click on the first link,
platform.openai.com.
In here, you need to log in with the
same account as using CHBD. So,
hopefully if you're watching this, you
have a CHGBD account. If not, you're
kind of falling behind. So, in top left,
click on login. Once you log in, click
on dashboard. On the left, click on API
keys. Create new secret key. I'm going
to name it NA10 follow upper. Boom.
Create secret key. Once again, do not
share these with anybody. Treat them as
passwords. I'm going to delete this key
before uploading this video. Go back to
NA10. Credentials. Create new
credential. Just paste your API key.
Save. It's testing it. Boom. Just like
that. Tested successfully. Which means
we can now use any of the OpenAI models.
And there is really like all of them.
You can use even GBD5. If you want to
use GPD5, you know, why not? Boom. There
we go. GPD5
select. So now we have the AI agent with
the chat model. The next thing is the
output, right? What does the agent do?
It needs to reply to the message aka
send an email. So let's click plus right
here after the agent output. We need to
find the line. Click plus. Do Gmail.
Select Gmail. And then reply. Reply to a
message. Okay. Select the first one. Let
me reorganize it a bit so it looks
nicer. Very important. Double click on
this once again. Select the same
account. resource message operation
reply message ID let's switch to
expression the email type switch that to
text there we go text and the message is
just going to be JSON output switch to
expression JSON output and that should
be it to be honest let's save that and
let's run this again so execute workflow
it's finding a message there was instant
now it's the AI agent is running with
open AI API okay GPD5 will take like a
few seconds to respond
So, this one is writing the email
obviously and then it's going to send
the email and the loop over again if we
have more items obviously because this
one can work um even if you have 20
emails right that you send out. Oh,
there we go. So, workflow has finished.
Let's check our email. Did this get a
follow-up. Okay. And I can already see
that it did which is beautiful. So, look
at this. Hey there, following up on my
note from the other day in case it
through. I'm happy to reset context.
Isn't this beautiful? We just got an AI
agent automatically follow up on an
email that I sent out. Now, obviously in
this case it was 38 minutes ago, but
imagine this was sent like a few days
ago, right? And it didn't get a
response. AI agent runs, follows up.
Amazing. Like this is going to save so
many hours in so many businesses and so
many jobs. It's crazy. This is not going
to replace jobs. A lot of people listen
to, you know, Sam Alman, Dario, these
people who hype up You have to
realize the CEOs of the companies, they
have the most incentive to hype
everything up. However, AI agents are
going to replace the most repetitive,
boring parts of your job. So, you can
focus on the creative stuff because
LLMs, news flash, are not creative and
it will not be solved just by scaling.
It will needs an entirely different
architecture. Why? Because large
language models are sequence models. All
they do is predict the next word aka the
next token. So, they cannot have a
inventive original thought like humans
can. So, what I'm trying to say is that
you don't have to worry for your job.
Instead, you should be excited that
agents like this can replace all the
boring in your job and you'll do
the creative high leverage stuff. And
again, this is just the first of the six
AI agents I'm going to show you. Plus,
later in the video, I'll show you how
you can actually make real money by
selling NAT agents like this one to
businesses for thousands of dollars.
However, in order to start building AI
agents, either for yourself or for other
businesses, you need to know how to host
them, which is one of the biggest
problems beginners face. Luckily, the
solution is quite simple and that is
Hostinger. This is what I use for all of
my AI agents, for all of the AI agents
we use in our team because it's the
simplest way you can start building AI
agents, plus one of the most affordable
ways as well. So, let me show you how to
set it up. If you get the KVM2 plan,
which I would recommend you to get, you
can literally run hundreds of AI agents
on this plan, and it will cost you way
less than if you used the NA10 Cloud,
especially if you go with the 24 month
option, which I definitely recommend you
do because you want your AI agents
running forever. You build them once and
they save you time in perpetuity. And
since Hostinger was kind enough to
sponsor this video, if you use the
coupon code David, you will save
additional 10% off on your annual or
2-year plan. Then what remains is
selecting the server location. So just
select whatever is closest to you. I'm
in Czech Republic, so Germany is super
close. And then for the operating
system, click on NA10. They literally
have a one-click install template for
NA10. It couldn't be any easier. So
click on confirm and then click on
continue and log in with your hosting
account or just create one. And the last
thing that remains is filling out your
billing details and your credit card.
I've been using Hostinger for months to
host my enter agents. And it really is
the simplest and most affordable way to
do so. So again, make sure to check out
the link description and remember to use
code David to get 10% off. All right. So
once you have your Hostinger VPS, go to
the panel, click on home, and select
manage. Here we can see how our virtual
private server is running and all the
usage you see about it. So this is
another advantage over the N10 cloud.
You can actually see this data that NA10
otherwise wouldn't give you. So all we
need to click is manage app and this
will launch the NA10 server where we can
see all of our AI agents. All right,
let's look at the second AI agent which
is realistic AI videos. And there is
hundreds of ways you can do this. You
can use it for marketing, for B-roll in
videos, for you know promotions like um
for uh interviews, for upskilling your
employees. I mean get creative. You know
realistic videos are changing the world.
There's like the startup Synasia I'm
going to pop up on screen that is
scaling like crazy. I think they're like
200 million ARR and all they do is like
create realistic video avatars, right?
So this automation is going to teach you
how to do that. It's actually pretty
simple. So trigger the trigger doesn't
really matter to be honest. Here I have
a schedule trigger. You can do WhatsApp,
Telegram, up to you. Trigger isn't the
main thing here. The main thing is
honestly the V3, but we're going to get
to that. Be patient. Second note is
Google Sheets, right? So, so this is
simple get rows in a sheet. You connect
Google Sheets API just like we did with
Gmail API earlier. Then resource click
on sheet within document operation get
rows and then document by URL. So here
is the doc for this and for this example
I'm going to keep it super simple and
I'm following a trend. It's actually
much bigger than I thought which is ASMR
videos. Right? So let me show you
example. So here's an example of a video
completely generated with AI including
the sound. So take a listen.
So yeah, this is ASMR. Uh to be honest,
I don't really watch or listen to ASMR,
but you'll be surprised how big the
market is. I mean, some of these videos
are getting hundreds of millions of
views, but again, you can use this
anyway. I'll show you how to customize
the prompt. So yeah, you attach the
Google sheet, then you select which
sheet because, you know, sheets have
different pages. So just select the
correct page. Then underneath filters
column, click on status and then value
start. So when this goes to start this
is when the automation will be triggered
right. So we can do like a marketing
video for a real estate company blah
blah blah whatever you want this is the
video ID release this is the prompt and
then you switch it to start and the
trigger will pick it up and under
combine filters select and and that's it
as you can see the Google sheets note is
pretty simple then we have a AI agent
and this guy is responsible for writing
the prompt. So whatever you write here,
you just put the video idea. This AI
agent has a prompt that is optimized for
creating. Well, this one again is for
ASMR, but you can style this for like
marketing videos, right? So you can say
marketing
marketing video copywriter, right?
Whatever you need for your own use case.
Feel free to update this prompt. But
basically, this turns the vague video
idea into an optimized prompt for V3,
which is the video model we're using.
Uh, in this case, we're using OpenAI
GBD4 mini. Again, whatever model you
prefer. My favorite is GBD4.1. It's more
powerful than the mini, and it's very
cheap as well. Let me save that
actually. And then this is the main
part, the HTTP request, right? So, what
does this do? Again, you might be
thinking, okay, David, I don't know what
HTTP is. Honestly, you don't even need
to understand what HTTP stands for. For
those who are curious, it's hypertext
transfer protocol. But the main thing is
is that we do a request to this URL.
Okay, so this is the URL where V3 is
hosted. We're using replicate for this.
Honestly, you can think of replicate as
kind of an open router but for videos
and AI images, right? But it's more than
that because you can actually host the
models here as well. Open router is just
the router. But as you can see here, we
already have V3 fast. We have some other
AI video models. Uh but for this we're
using Google V3. This is the most
powerful version of Google's video
model. And look at this realism, right?
You upload an image and then it gives
you a realistic video which you could
easily fool a lot of people with this.
So in here, if you click on HTTP, you
get instructions on how to do the
request, right? You see the
authorization be better token. You see
the headers. You see the prompt right
here. Resolution aspect ratio. So
replicate gives you everything you need.
And all you can also use it in Python,
NodeJS, whatever you want. So this is
the power of replicate and it makes it
very easy where you don't have to host
these models yourself. Right? So we're
using a basic HTTP request to the
replicate URL. And then just like I
said, we send the headers specify them
exactly as they are specified right
here. So, authorization and we put the
bearer token and this is actually your
replicate API key. So, do not share this
with anybody. I'm going to have to
delete mine after upload or before
uploading this video. Hopefully, I don't
forget. But yeah, this is your API key.
So, it looks like this or whatever
whatever whatever. And just if you're
curious, you can create this in your
account. So, click on your account,
click on API tokens here. Put your uh
API name. So, I can put like VO free
agent and just create token. Now, I
think you get a few dollars for free,
but if it doesn't work, just charge up
like $3 and you'll be fine. Just keep in
mind if you want to create hundreds of
videos with V3, it is more expensive
than languages, right? Generating videos
is more expensive than generating text.
So, you know, keep that in mind. The
costs are $320 per 8second video. So, if
you are completely broke, this agent is
not for you. But if you have that
hustle, if you have that entrepreneurial
resourcefulness, you can flip these
videos for hundreds of dollars. Like you
can sell video creatives for companies.
You can sell mockups like interior
design, walkthroughs, digital. Like
there's infinite opportunity, guys.
Literally infinite. All you need to have
is a bit of initiative and the slightest
bit of work ethic and you can make it.
You can make so much money with AI. It's
kind of disgusting. So this is the setup
for the headers. again authorization
better API key name prefer value weight
send body and then body content type
JSON specify body using JSON and by the
way if you pay attention this JSON is
literally this part of the HTTP request
right so N10 just makes it a bit simpler
by splitting it into multiple fields but
you get the point right so here we need
this is important we actually cannot
send the new lines so by doing u this a
little bit of reg x you know that
replace we replace these new line
characters because that's one thing that
replicate doesn't really like. So yeah,
just make sure there's new line no new
line characters when you're sending
this. And that's pretty much it for the
HTTP request. It's not that difficult.
And actually, I can put something here.
Let me flip this to start. We can flip
this to finish. I can say um strawberry
in the spirit of, you know, strawberry
for OpenAI. Let's create a video about a
strawberry. Let's go step by step.
Schedule trigger. Let's run this.
Successful. Get rows in sheet. Boom. So,
this got Yeah, correct. Nice. We're
going to send this to the AI agent. The
agent is going to write the prompt for
this. Next up, HTTP request. This one is
going to create a video. Then, it's
going to be sent to this one, which is
another HTTP request. And this basically
streams the the output. That's it. This
doesn't really do anything else. Method
get URL JSON URL stream. Maybe there's a
simpler way to do it, but hey, this
works, you know. If you know of a better
way, feel free to comment below. And by
the way, if you want to see more NA10
videos, make sure to subscribe. You
would be surprised how strong of a
signal that is. It takes like two
seconds to subscribe. It's completely
free and it tells me you like this type
of content. So if you want to see more
NA10 videos on your YouTube recommended
page, go below the video and subscribe
right now. So again, this one we
covered. This one I showed you just now.
It streams the output and then it
uploads it to Google Drive. Resource
file operation upload input data field
name data file name. This honestly
doesn't matter much, but here we just
have it for the video idea. So, it
matches the video idea. That's the file
name. And then you put my drive and the
URL folder. Pretty simple. Just like
other Google notes. If you learn a few
of these um Google services, Gmail,
sheets, you'll be able to do all of
them. Whether it's calendar, whether
it's u Google Drive, whether it's I
don't know what else. What else is in
the guitue? They have so many services.
It's crazy. If you learn a few of them,
you can do all of them. Basically NA10
is really compounding like that and then
Google sheets up update row and sheet.
So overall this agent again is simple.
This is six simple agents all people
should have. So you know it's nothing
crazy but you can see this is very
powerful because you could have your
client post stuff here and you could
maybe charge them you know $50 per video
where it's costing you $320 per video.
Very nice arbitrage and a lot of people
in the new society are actually doing
business models like this. You know,
everybody wants to make like 10k a month
with AI, but a lot of people just want
to make $2,000 as a multiple sources of
income. You know, like a lot of people
have a job and they don't want to quit
it. They just want to have a second
source of income with AI. It's totally
possible and I've seen it dozens of
times. So, let's run it. We have the We
have the prompt. Let's look at a wrote a
detailed prompt for how it should sound,
how it should look like. Then, we're
running replicate. This one is the
longest one because it's generating the
video. usually takes between 30 and 60
seconds from my testing. Okay, there we
go. Video has been generated. If we look
at this, we have this output.
So this node kind of simplifies that
just rereams it into a file name. So we
actually have the file with 2.4
megabytes which we can then upload into
Google Drive. So that's why this node is
necessary. It's kind of just formatting
for Google Drive. Let's run it.
Uploading the file also takes a few
seconds. since it's on a server and then
it just updates the row in a sheet
because right now we have um the start
and we don't have the link. So this
should update the sheet so that this is
flipped to finished and we have the
link. Beautiful. Let's look at the
video.
Man, the sounds are so realistic. That's
crazy. And yeah, this is um
hyperrealistic
AI video using the best AI model in the
world. And again, feel free to customize
this prompt. All you need to do is
change the prompt of this AI agent to be
optimized for marketing, recruiting, uh
video creatives, whatever types of
videos you want to make. B-roll for
YouTube videos, faceless YouTube
channels, you can start with this. I
mean, the opportunities are endless,
right? Just customize this prompt so
that it generates videos that you want
and that's pretty much it. You can get
started with it using the best video
model in the world. Now, if you think
generating hyperrealistic videos with
matching sound is impressive, just wait
until you see what's coming. So here is
the first simple AI agent everybody
needs and this one has a bit more nodes
but it's actually pretty simple. So let
me walk through. So here we actually
have two schedule triggers. This one is
running every 11 hours. And basically
what this agent does is tracking a
YouTube channel's performance very very
accurately. So maybe you have some
competitors or maybe you want to track
your own channel. Doesn't matter. Or
maybe you want to sell this to a client.
You know there's plenty of YouTubers who
would buy something like this. I mean,
if you showed me this like a few months
back before I really locked in on any
10, I would definitely pay $500,000
minimum because you'll see these reports
that this agent generates are very, very
detailed with graphs and stuff. So,
basically, this trigger runs every 11
hours. It checks the RSS feed. So, this
is my channel as an example, but u yeah,
it just checks my videos. Then, we have
a code block which filters out all the
items to only the ones published in the
last 12 hours. So we don't want to be
retracting the same videos over and
over. So that's what this code block
does. To be honest, if you are scared of
code blocks, you can probably like use
some of these um default ones, data
transformation like edit fields, filter,
stuff like that. But a lot of the times
it's just simpler to go to JBD, ask it
to write the code and use a single
JavaScript code block than, you know,
five different manual NAN logics and
loops and conditionals. It's up to you.
whatever you want. Next, we have a
Google Sheets append row in sheet. So,
this actually sets the status to start.
So, here you know, boom, start. And this
is how it looks like, by the way. So,
you can see this is measuring like which
videos are performing on day one, day
three, day um yeah, 1 2 3 7 14 30 which
shows you outliers, which is very very
important to know like maybe your own
channel or your competitors which videos
are outliers. You can study those. You
can think of similar ideas, stuff like
that, right? So, this this agent is very
powerful and again lots of YouTubers
would pay some serious money to have it
and it's building is much simpler than
it might seem. So, again, this uh append
wrote in sheets sets the status to start
sets the video title sets the video
link. So, boom title link. Then we have
another Google Sheets note and this one
gets rows. So same document but the
filter is that it gets all the rows
where the status is at start. So it
ignores the finished ones and it ignores
the empty ones only when there's start
it runs on those basically. Then we have
edit fields and these are the fields to
set. So row number we do JSON row number
and link JSON video link which is
matching from the sheet. So then we have
a few familiar fields again we've
covered these AI agent into update rows
in Google Sheets. But this is where it
gets interesting. Day zero. So here we
have a YouTube node that gets the video
and its views based on the video ID. So
on YouTube every video has ID. Pull up
my latest uh so this is the correct
video, right? You can see this. This is
the video ID in the URL. And this note
gets the views. Then we have a update
row in sheets. So classic Google sheets
row number and then it sets the views on
day one. So in this sheet I'm using fake
data because I didn't want to run this
for 30 days um for obvious reasons. But
yeah, you can see this updates the views
day zero which updates our chart over
here. So for each video this runs and
then something interesting happens. Wait
one day. So this is very interesting
note. Um it literally just waits, you
know. So it's kind of like the schedule
but for a pause. So it pauses the
automation for one and then the unit is
days and then that's day zero and then
on day one it runs again gets the video
updates the rows on how many views it
has in day one and pauses for one day.
So then we have day two which is
basically the same. We track the views
we update the row for day two aka the
column and then we wait one day for day
three. On day three we do a longer pause
until day seven. Again you can configure
this however you want. If you want to
track every single day for 30 days it's
up to you. But I think uh 0 1 2 3 4 7
1430. That's really good. So basically
this is it. This is um this is the whole
thing. And as you can see even though
there's a lot of nodes it's quite
simple. I mean most of it is kind of
duplicated here with just a delay. And
this automation runs for 30 days until
it's completed. So it's literally inside
of NA10 sitting this execution is going
to be active for 30 days until it's
fully fully done. and it's going to be
tracking all of the views on this
channel. So again, for experimentations
using my own channel. So it's going to
be spotting which are outliers like this
NA10 video for example and which videos
are lacking. And then you can go back
and analyze why did the video flop, why
did this video do well and to any
content creator, this is beyond
valuable. Honestly, like I was being
very conservative when I say $500. to
bigger creators, something like this
could be worth thousands of dollars
because each successful video is going
to make them thousands of dollars. So,
if you can, you know, deliver them one
successful video every 3 months, right?
Every three months is like the ROI on AI
agent like this is kind of crazy. And
again, this is just number three of the
six that I'm going to show you in this
video. So, let's go on onto the next
one. Now, this one has a lot fewer
nodes, but that doesn't mean it's not
useful. It's actually just as useful.
And when I say everyone should have
this, I mean it. Everyone should have
this expense tracker agent. So you can
pretty much understand how it works just
by looking at it. But basically the
trigger is a Gmail note. So you select
which email you want to check. You do
pull times every minute or whatever you
want. And then event is message
received. So when a message comes in
into your email inbox, it will trigger
and it will run an AI agent which will
determine, hey, is this an expense or is
this just spam or some friend emailing
you or whatever, right? So the prompt I
again just like last time identical and
the prompt is this analyze email
personality silent dismiss honestly it's
pretty overkill. Uh the prompts you just
say like if this is an expense do that
if it's not an expense do nothing. This
prompt could be much shorter, but feel
free to take it, copy it. Again, all of
the resources are in the new society
templates and presets. So, if you want
any of these agents, like maybe this one
you could build very relatively fast.
The previous one took some time, but uh
if you want them and just literally just
one click import from file, all of that
is in the new society templates and
presets right here. AI agents by David.
You can download any of these and start
having that agent save you time right
away. literally with a few clicks, no
matter what your business or your life
is. Some of these agents every single
person needs expense tracker is one of
them. So again, this AI agents
determines is this an email with an
invoice, is this a receipt or is this
just some random ass email? For the
model, GPD 4.1 Minute is sufficient. If
you are finding issues that the model is
underperforming, just select 4.1 and
you're going to be chilling. And the
only tool it has is append row in
sheets. So all it does is just append a
single row in Google Sheets. Let me show
you. Could not be simpler.
Boom. There it is. So you have the date,
self-explanatory, date of the
transaction, the category. Honestly, the
category should probably be here. So the
transaction name, then the cost
category, and then how relevant it is.
This is like AI each ranks this 1
through 10. So if it's like a completely
waste um you know like Netflix
subscription might be two. If it's like
groceries might be nine, right? So you
understand this and yeah that's the AI
agent literally could not be simpler and
it automates most of your accounting
needs. Like obviously if you're like a
financial company, you probably need
in-house accountants. But if you're just
a single solarreneur, if you're a small
business owner, if you're a individual
and you just want to have a spreadsheet
with all your transactions categorized
into different categories and with the
relevance that the AI agent decides,
it could not be any simpler. It takes 5
to 10 minutes to build this and it's
going to save you time forever in
perpetuity. Now, let's be honest. The
reason you're watching this is because
you understand the power of automation
and AI agents. But one thing that nobody
is automating is the actions in their
productivity app, which is exactly what
we just released inside of vectal by
adding workflows. There's a lot of
manual that happens in your task
management, in your productivity. Now
you're able to automate it. So inside of
Veectal on the right there is this new
button workflows. In here you can either
use one of the pre-built workflows we
have or create a new one. Daily creative
idea. The trigger, let's go with
schedule. Daily at 8 a.m. And action
create idea. And you can set the prompt
to whatever you want. Maybe you run a
marketing agency. Maybe you do sales.
Maybe you have a fashion design
business, whatever you want. This
workflow will run every single day at 8
a.m. and create an actionable idea that
would get you closer to your goals. And
since Vectal has your user context such
as your word description, short-term
goals, long-term goals, this idea will
be hyper relevant to you. Now, this is
just one of many workflows you're able
to build inside of Veectal. For example,
this one is super useful and it's one of
the pre-built workflows that we built
for you. So, you don't even have to
build it when you use Vectal. So, what
it does, it runs every time an email is
received that fits this criteria, spam,
promotional email, stuff like that. And
then what to do? It marks the email as
red. This single workflow will reduce
the time you spend on your email by 80
to 90%. I have this running on all of my
main inboxes and it's something that
everyone should activate. So if you love
NA10, you're going to absolutely love
Vectal Workflows which allows you to
automate all the boring inside of
your task manure app. So go to vectal.ai
and give it a shot. You can use
workflows even on the free account. So
there is no excuse. Now let's go back to
any. The fifth agent all of you should
have is a personalized outreach email
agent. So all of us at a certain point
in our life need to send an email right
to somebody whether it's a company we're
applying to work at or you know someone
we want to have on a podcast but that
email cannot be basic it cannot be spam
it needs to be personalized and this is
exactly what this agent does. So we have
a schedule trigger right here which
checks again rows inside of a sheet. So
here is what the sheet looks like. We
have the research status. We have the
email. So this is my email for testing.
uh contact company could be vectal
doesn't matter contact name and then the
research. So this is what this agent
does. It does deep research on that
person before sending the email. So if
you're doing cold emails, this will
change the game completely for you. And
um yeah, I'm going to show you how to
build this. So you have the full
personalized email body just by this
little bit of information. All you need
is the contact email and the name of the
person really. So again, this trigger
runs I think it's one once a day. Yeah,
it doesn't really matter. And it checks
all the new leads here. You can set it
to one once an hour. It's up to you.
Schedule trigger is very easy to
configure, you know. Boom. Runs once an
hour just like that. Next gets rows in
sheets. So it gets all the rows with the
start status just like the previous
agents. And then this is interesting. So
you can use either perplexity owner or
there's an alternative way SER API. It's
up to you whichever you prefer. Um some
people are familiar with SER some people
prefer perplexity. So whatever you
whichever you want to use you can use it
just you know detach the other one and
attach this as the chart model entirely
up to you. Then this agent performs web
research. So again either it uses
proplexity or SER but it researches on
this person and the prompt is the main
thing right?
You are a research assistant. Your task
is to perform photo web research on a
specified person and or company. So
there's some more info but that's
basically it. It does deep research on
this person and the company to
understand who it does what it's about
enough info to personalize the email and
then it goes into second AI agent. So
this one writes the email, right? So it
it gets all the info from the previous
agent and the research results. So
actually this is from the sheet and this
is the research results for the previous
agent and it's instructed to write a
personalized collab email as me you know
David you can obviously customize this
prompt however you want again all of the
AI agents from this video are available
in the new society inside of the
templates and preset section. So if you
want to just take the prompts or if you
want to import the whole agent you you
know where to find them. So yeah first
agent does the web search agent writes
the email and then we update the rows in
a sheet. So actually this is the
practical way of doing it. A lot of
people would have it send the email
right away. But this AI agents are not
there yet. Maybe in a year, maybe in two
years where they're like super reliable,
but LLMs hallucinate. LLMs make up
So the way to do it is to have one step
human approval, right? So if you add
like let's say again you can have a
separate agent that does the lead
generation that scrapes the web for
emails and adds the contact names and
then you you launch it once a day you
know the next 10 people are researched
and then the email is written for them
and then you go as a human or you hire a
VA or whatever just double checking that
the email is looking good right maybe if
if it's like if you're doing crazy
volume and you you don't care you can
remove this step but I think for most
most production and most real businesses
you will need to confirm the email that
the AI wrote and maybe instead of doing
that you can actually have a you can
actually have a separate step Gmail and
it can be a draft right create a draft
so that's another way to do it it's just
probably easier to see many of them in a
sheet so if you're doing lots of volumes
saving that in a sheet is easier if
you're doing less volume writing a draft
and then just sending it through an
email you know going to your drafts and
you'll see the pre-written drafts here
and just clicking send probably is
easier. Then the send out of the email
is once you approve it, right? So once
you confirm the status to confirmed, the
second part of the automation runs again
I think once a day or once five minutes
doesn't matter and uh sends out all the
emails that you confirmed. So it gets
the rows by confirmed and it sends the
message and it up updates it to send.
So, this agent, it has a few more nodes
than the previous one, but it's also
very simple and it's beyond useful,
especially for businesses that are doing
cold outreach and that are sending out
lots of emails. This makes sure that the
email is personalized and that it
doesn't get you get higher delivery
rates, higher open rates, and ultimately
more business. That's the goal of this.
And you save yourself time and your
team's time. This agent can be obviously
used in hundreds of different ways, but
if you're doing anything with cold email
outreach, you need an AI agent like this
one. Now, as I promised, I'm going to
also talk about how to turn this into a
side hustle because you can make a lot
of money relatively fast with AI agents.
I mean, these are some offers that
people are offering and I would say
these are not even experts. These are
like medium level AI agent builders,
right? And you can see the start package
750 and advanced package is 5K and
businesses are paying way more than that
for good AI agents and automations. But
the mistake a lot of people make is that
they don't stand out. You know they like
AI automation agency. No no no business
wants to hear that. If someone reaches
out to me and say like I run an AI
automation agency they instantly get
flagged by my vectoral workflow as spam,
right? Because this is a this is not an
original offer. Nobody wants to work
with an AI automation agency. People
want to be solving, they want you to
solve a specific problem for them. You
need to be specialized. A good way to
stand out is to have an irresistible
offer. And the example like how you can
do that is add a free AI consultation
for an expert. You need to position
yourself as expert, right? So this is
much harder to say no to than oh I'm AI
agency. You know this is I charge this
much. If you just offer a free
consultation with no expectations and
you actually do a lot of preparation
beforehand, maybe you use one of your
agents to help you with the preparation
and the deep research, the company will
be way more impressed. If you put 5
hours of effort into a free
consultation, be like, "Oh, wow. This
guy, this guy did a lot for this, you
know, free call. Like, imagine if I hire
him, he'll probably overd deliver."
That's the type of feeling you need to
leave in your clients. Then to profit
maximize, you want to add some expensive
but great add-ons, right? And this is
where the real money is because business
owners value time. They value speed.
They value efficiency, personalization.
So this is example of someone on Upwork
to doing this today and there's no
reason it could be you. These people are
not experts in machine learning or
experts in math or programming. You
literally have to click and drag in a
tool like NA10 to do this. So this
person which we found is doing the fast
delivery for another 5 to 500 to 100k.
So if you have a bit of work ethic and
you can deliver fast, you can charge
another 1k done for you code. You know
if people want any u automation but in
code boom another 1500 and how can you
do that? Tools like cloth code tools
like codex tools like cursor I've made
countless videos on these. So if you're
subscribed to this channel you will
know. Code guidance is literally could
just be a call explaining the code to
them and how to integrate it. Another
500. Do you see the upsells are crazy?
That's because this guy knows that a
businessman will happily spend money to
save time for the fast delivery or
happily spend time to, you know, get his
business up to speed with the code
guidance. So really being creative with
the bonuses, with the guarantees, with
the conditions this is where you can
make your offer stand out from everybody
else. I mean this is what Hermosi talks
about. So if you follow, if you follow
Alexi, if you read the book 100 million
offers, you will know all of this. But
applying this for AI agents is where the
untapped opportunity is because this
field is very new and most people have
such a boring commoditized offer. It's
crazy. So what do you need to take away?
It's not about creating the most
complicated agent. Far from it, guys.
All you need is a reliable agent that
specifically targets the business and
helps to solve a specific problem for
that business. Like you don't even need
to show them the notes. It could
literally be four nodes, five nodes. It
could take you an hour to build. Doesn't
matter. It's more about creating a great
offer specific to your target avatar. So
if you're targeting dentists, if you're
targeting real estate agents, whoever it
is you're specializing on, it is all
about the offer. The offer needs to be
compelling. It needs to reverse risk. It
needs to deliver the promise fast. You
need to understand Zatar, what problems
they're facing, what is their dream
outcome. If you don't, you will always
struggle. If you don't, if you do
understand it, you will have more
clients than you can handle. So this is
how you can turn any on missions into
business. Now let me show you the sixth
agent that everyone needs and this one I
really believe everyone needs. So this
agent unlike the other ones which are
more business targeted is for your
personal life to never ever miss a
person's birthday. Right? So you have a
Google sheet once again. Let me show
you. Boom. Where you write down the
birthdays of your friends. Right? So
birthday name interest and actually you
only need to add the let me make it
clear. You only need to add these three
fields, birthday, name, and interest.
The agent takes care of the rest of the
gift ideas and of reminding you. So, if
you have a calendar or some place where
you store all your closest friends
birthdays, you just once add them here
and then we have a schedule trigger.
Honestly, we could probably have it run
uh less frequently
because uh maybe like once a week.
You'll see the way this AI agent works.
Basically what this agent does is that
not only does it remind you of the
birthday when it's coming like up to
seven days before so you have enough
time to buy the gift but also
brainstorms some gift ideas right so it
reads get rows in sheet classic Google
sheet where you have the status as
nothing so this is important you have to
actually set it like so status value
empty otherwise it it doesn't work then
you have the AI agent which brainstorms
the based on the interest It brainstorms
ideas right based on the name. If it's a
man or a woman, maybe the gift ideas are
different. And if the birthday is within
7 days, it will generate the idea using
a model. So you can use a reasoning
model. If you prefer cloth as ideas, you
know, disconnect openai and connect
anthropic pretty simple change. You just
need to add your uh enthropic API key.
That's the only change. And then we have
a tool structured output parser to
format the output of the agent. Then we
have if else note. So you know a lot of
people use AI agents for simple
conditional logic which is very bad. You
should absolutely use code where
possible. And if else statement is a
beautiful example of that. So don't be
one of these people who spend $1,200 a
month on LLM doing simple Right?
So this was a Reddit post like wow we've
been burning money for 6 months. We're
spending $1,200 a month. And what was
what was they doing? You think, okay,
some crazy AI agent like writing
personalized emails, like really doing
lots of reasoning. No, this person was
extracting phone numbers from text,
which you can do with regular
expression. He was checking profanity,
which you can do matching words against
the blacklist. He was reformatting JSON.
There is countless of JSON parsers that
exist. And he was, this one is the
funniest. He was using the LLM to
uppercase words which literally you can
do with that upper a single method. So
there's a lot of people who are quite
stupid who are using LLMs for things
that you should be using code for. And
this person was spending 1,200 a month
and and he was posting this like wow
look at this optimization after
switching to GPD photo mini we the bills
dropped to $200 a month. No, you're
still a dumbass. You're spending $200 a
month on something that should be a
simple code that costs nearly zero to
run. You can do this all with Python or
JavaScript for nearly zero. It can run
super fast, more reliable, by the way,
than LLM because LM hallucinate and
infinitely faster because a response
from LM can take 1, two, 3 seconds.
Python can run in a few milliseconds.
Same with JavaScript. So don't be one of
these people who avoid code at all cost
and then look like absolute retards when
they use LLMs for this. and spend
hundreds of dollars a month on stuff
that has been solved for decades with a
few lines of code. So this is what I
mean. We can use an if statement here. A
lot of people would use a AI
agent here. It's like, okay, if it's
true, redirect to Telegram. If it's
false, like guys, come on. No matter if
you're not a beginner programmer, it's
all about constructing logic. It's not
about being a senior developer. An AI
agent is really good at like recognizing
if email is spam or not, right? based on
the context of the email, who sent it,
how it was phrased. There's a lot of
different like variables and nuances
that goes into that. You cannot just use
a black list of words, right? Because
that would be unreliable and it would do
false flags. So, use AI where it makes
sense. But if you can solve something
with a few lines of code, use code for
that, right? And the beauty of NA10 is
that a lot of the code is actually a
place replaced with these nodes. So, you
have these like data transformation
nodes where a lot of them like edit
fields, right? set modify, add or remove
fields, filter, remove fields, matching
conditions, limit the these are all like
logic that otherwise you would have to
write code. But thanks to NA10, you
don't have to do that. You have these
pre-built, pre-created nodes that you
can just click and drag and drop. And
again, all you need to do is kind of
think through the logic in your brain.
And once you know how your AI agent or
AI automation should work, you can build
it just with these notes. Instead of
putting AI agent everywhere where it
doesn't make sense. So again, if it's
true that the birthday is coming up, we
send a text message on Telegram
reminding you that, hey, your friend's
birthday is coming up. I mean, look, to
be honest, this is mostly for men,
right? Let's be honest. Women, they all
always somehow remember their friend's
birthday up to like two months before
they're preparing for it. It's crazy how
much effort they put into this So,
this is mostly for us guys. um so that
we don't forget about one of our best
friends birthdays and the AI agent also
brainstorms the gift idea. If you want
more ideas, just change the prompt to
brainstorm five different ideas. One of
them is most likely going to be
relevant. And yeah, this AI agent,
unlike the other ones, is for your
personal life, but it will allow you to
be one of the favorite guys in the group
because you never miss a birthday and
you always have a per ready when one of
your boys birthday comes. So yeah, this
AI agent is also something that everyone
should have just in case. Even if you're
great with birthdays, it never hurts to
be reminded. So yeah, these were six AI
agents that everyone should have. And
again, the beauty of NA10 is that once
you build your first agent, you you
defeat most of the friction. It's it can
be intimidating at the start, but if you
really get started, if you really push
through to the first one or two agents,
the rest is really easy because you you
do the same right? Schedule
trigger. We've learned that Google
Sheet, we've learned that AI agent, we
know that. So like most of the notes
you're already familiar with. So really,
I would encourage you to sit down, block
out 60 to 90 minutes in your calendar
and build your first NAT agent. This is
a beyond valuable skill to have in the
next few years. It will future proof
yourself against being replaced because
if you can in your company be the guy
who finds a way to automate the process,
trust me, no boss is going to ever fire
you. So yeah, this has been six AI
agents that everybody needs. And again,
once you build agents, you need to host
them somewhere. And the best option is
by far Hostinger is the simplest way.
It's like literally one click. You don't
have to know anything about VPS
management. None of that. They make it
so easy to run self-hosted NA10 on a
VPS. And it's also one of the most
affordable options out there. So once
again, thank you Hostinger for
sponsoring the video. Make sure to use
code David for another 10% off when
going with the annual or Twitter plan.
And with that being said, thank you guys
for watching and have a wonderful,
productive week.